Evan Parker

evancp@hotmail.com 07951994183 London

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a creative individual, who is passionate about technology, all things digital, and cultural experiences. I have broad experience in the museum and culture sectors, specifically with arts/project management, and more recent experience with web/app development.

WORK HISTORY

Cultural Events Assistant

August 2017 - Present

Permanent British Library London

- -Assisting with the delivery, planning and administration of the Library's Cultural Events programme, including late openings, talks, theatre shows, music gigs, festivals and more
- Working closely with internal and external stakeholders, including partners, artists, and event participants, publishers, agents, external production companies, partners, etc.
- -Working with the Corporate Events manager to set up and manage high profile exhibition private views and patron events
- -Managing budgets, processing invoices and purchase orders -Processing contracts and rights forms
- -Working to 'What's On' brochure deadlines, including copywriting, image research, proofing, working closely with Marketing
- Working with the web development team to build an event archive, showcasing years of Cultural Event video material
- Working with the Library's CMS to regularly update the website with engaging content

Barbican Centre Host

February 2015 - Present

Part time Barbican Centre London

- Working on busy classical music and theatre shows.
- Working in the Art Gallery on busy exhibitions

Learning and New Talent Assistant

June 2015 - January 2016

BAFTA

- Updating the BAFTA website with new content
- Managing a weekly members newsletter

• Assisting with film screenings and public talks

EDUCATION

BA Degree

University of East London - 2011 Creative Writing 2:1

A-Level

Graveney Sixth Form - 2006 Media, English Literature, Sports Studies B,B,C

GCSE

Graveney School - 2004

English, Maths, Science, IT, Geography, RS, Resistant Materials 6 A's, 3 C's

TRAINING & CERTIFICATIONS

Juice Academy Python for Librarians Juice Academy	May 2022
Udemy Full Stack Developer 2022 Udemy	April 2022
Intermediate JavaScript Nanodegree Udacity	February 2022
React JS Nanodegree Udacity	November 2021
Front End Development General Assembly	July 2021

SKILLS

Administration, Project Management, Customer Service, Copywriting, React JS, JavaScript, Python, Node JS/Express, HTML, CSS, MongoDB, SQL, Sass, Bootstrap

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

